A Guide to the Studies of the Virginia Division of Legislative Services, 1978-2000.
Library of Virginia
- Studies (Accession 40083), 1987-1999., Extent: 22 cubic feet (22 boxes)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Meeting, 1998 Aug 18. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Meeting, 1998 Oct 20. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - General information, 1998. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Consumer, Environment and Education Task Force meeting, 1998 Aug 18. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Consumer, Environment and Education Task Force meeting, 1998 Sept 17. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Consumer, Environment and Education Task Force meeting, 1998 Oct 6. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Drafting Group Work Session, 1999 Jan 6. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - State and Local Taxation TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Sept 15. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - State and Local Taxation TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Oct 1. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - State and Local Taxation TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Nov 4. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - State and Local Taxation TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Nov 24. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Structure and Transition TAsk Force meeting, 1998 May 26. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Structure and Transition TAsk Force meeting, 1998 June 15. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Structure and Transition TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Aug 12. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Structure and Transition TAsk Force meeting, 1998 Sept 11. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 Sept 29. (Box 18)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 Nov 7. (Box 18)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 Dec 17. (Box 18)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - State Corporation Commission Model for Restructuring the Electric Utility Industry (Draft), 1997 Nov 7. (Box 18)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Correspondence/related material, 1997. (Box 18)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 Mar 25. (Box 19)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 July 15-16. (Box 19)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Meeting, 1997 Aug 18. (Box 19)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Publications and reports, 1997. (Box 20)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Coal and Energy Commission / Energy Preparedness Subcommittee, 1995 June 12. (Box 19)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Coal and Energy Commission / Energy Preparedness Subcommittee, 1995 Oct 16. (Box 19)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 259) - Coal and Energy Commission / Energy Preparedness Subcommittee, 1995 Dec 18. (Box 19)
  - Higher Education Institution Retirement Plan Exemptions (HB 2449), 1997 Dec. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission, 1997-1998. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1997 June 11. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1997 July 31. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1997 Oct 1. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Annual report, 1997. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Annual report, 1998. (Box 20)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1995 Dec 14. (Box 21)
  - Small Business Commission - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 21)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1996 June 17. (Box 21)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1996 July 23. (Box 21)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1996 Sept 10. (Box 21)
  - Small Business Commission - Meeting, 1996 Oct 3. (Box 21)
- Studies (Accession 40914), 1973-1998., Extent: 27 cubic feet (27 boxes)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Analysis of proposed changes, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Chart comparing present law and Board proposals for standards, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Chart of alternative version of Standards of Quality considered by the Board of Education, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: After school programs, 1984. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1974. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1977. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1980. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Impace aid and school finance developments, 1984. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Initital Staff Study, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Materials, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1976. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1978. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Correspondence, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Materials from the Dept. of Education and notes from Board meeting, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Minutes and agendas, 1975. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Minutes and agendas, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Minutes and agendas, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Miscellaneous materials, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Regular bill materials, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Standards of Quality, 1983. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Standards of Quality, 1984. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Standards of Quality, 1987. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Standards of Quality - Miscellaneous, 1987. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Transcripts of public hearings, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League, 1986. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League - Correspondence, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League - Correspondence, 1986. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League - Material, 1980. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League - Minutes, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Standards of Quality: Virginia High School League - Reports, 1986. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study the Feasibility of Establishing a Residential School for Gifted Students at Montpelier (HJR 119): Correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study the Feasibility of Establishing a Residential School for Gifted Students at Montpelier (HJR 119): Notes, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study the Feasibility of Establishing a Residential School for Gifted Students at Montpelier (HJR 119): Statutes, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Articles, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Minutes and reports, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Materials - Independent living, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Materials - Insurance, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Materials - Minority health, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Materials - Other states, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Materials - School Health Education, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Notes, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Statistics, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Means of Reducing Preventable Death and Disability in the Commonwealth and to Examine the Fearsibility of Implementing a Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia (HJR 179): Statutes, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Materials - Election of school boards, 1989. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Materials - School Dropout, 1990. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Materials - School dropout and self-esteem, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Materials - School dropout, 1989. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Meetings - School dropout, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Reports, 1989. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Report, 1990. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Task Force on Education, Programming and Funding, 1989. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Task Force on Self-Esteem - Notes, 1989-1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Schools Dropout and Ways to Promote the Development of Self-Esteem: Task Force on Self-Esteem, 1989-1992. (Box 5)
  - Subcommittee on the Education of the Deaf and Blind - Records (meetings, reports, court cases, correspondence, public hearing comments), 1975-1978. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Issue of Determination of Eligibility for Reduced Tuition Charges in the Commonwealth's Institutions of Higher Education - Records (Reports, correspondence, research materials), 1983-1984. (Box 6)
  - Subcommittee on Education - Charter Schools - Correspondence, 1995-1996. (Box 7)
  - Subcommittee on Education - Charter Schools - Notes and presentations, 1995-1996. (Box 7)
  - Subcommittee on Education - Charter Schools - Research materials, 1995-1996. (Box 7)
  - Subcommittee on Education - Charter Schools - Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 7)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Christopher Newport, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - George Mason University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - James Madison University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Longwood, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Mary Washington, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Norfolk State University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Old Dominion University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Radford, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - University of Virginia, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Virginia Military Institute, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Virginia State University, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - William and Mary, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Miscellaneous (Correspondence, Clinch Valley, Richard Bland, VCCS), 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Reports, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Stone Commission) - Shaner Report, 1972-1974. (Box 8)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Agendas and meetings, 1991. (Box 10)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Correspondence, 1991. (Box 10)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Reports, 1991. (Box 10)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Research materials, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Education Task Force, 1990-1992. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Presentations, 1990. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Correspondence, 1990. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Public hearings, 1991. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Notes (HJR 106), undated. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Report approvals, 1992. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Research materials, 1990-1992. (Box 11)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Notes, 1992. (Box 12)
  - Southside Economic Development Commission - Research materials, 1990-1995. (Box 12)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence (HJR 71), 1992. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/Meetings (HJR 71), 1992. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials (HJR 71), 1992. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials (HJR 71), 1993. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence (HJR 71), 1993. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence (HJR 353), 1994. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/meetings (HJR 353), 1994. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Notes (HJR 353), 1994. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials (HJR 353), 1994. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/meetings/notes (HJR 451), 1995. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence (HJR 451), 1995. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials (HJR 451), 1995. (Box 13)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - HJR 106, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - HJR 300, 1991. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/meetings, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/meetings, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - HJR 101, 1997. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Agendas/meetings, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Research materials, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Report (HJR 451), 1996. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Appomattox, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Buckingham, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Campbell, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Charlotte, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Danville, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Franklin, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Franklin, City of, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Henry, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Mecklenburg, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Patrick, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Pittsylvania, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Prince Edward, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - South Boston, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Southampton, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Sussex, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (A.L. Philpott) - Virginia Heartland, 1994-1995. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Research materials, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Report approvals, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Correspondence, 1992-1993. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Research materials, 1992. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Miscellaneous, 1992. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1992. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Increased Mortality and Cancer Rates Among Firefighters - Research materials and reports, 1992-1993. (Box 16)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission - Correspondence, 1994-1998. (Box 17)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1994-1998. (Box 17)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission - Reports, 1994-1998. (Box 17)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission - Articles, 1994-1998. (Box 17)
  - Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission - Handouts, 1994-1998. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Remedial Summer School Programs (HJR 529) - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Remedial Summer School Programs (HJR 529) - Presentations and handouts, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Remedial Summer School Programs (HJR 529) - Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Remedial Summer School Programs (HJR 529) - Research materials, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Remedial Summer School Programs (HJR 529) - Study plans/objectives, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Correspondence, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Legislation, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Presentations/Handouts, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Women's Access to Obstetrical and Gynecological Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Research materials, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Continuation of Services to Young Adults Exiting Publicly Funded Prograns (HJR 103) - Agendas/meetings/minutes, 1994. (Box 17)